<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cryptography on Juniperspring</title>
    <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/tags/cryptography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cryptography on Juniperspring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juniperspring.xyz/tags/cryptography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Directional Authentication with TOTP</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/bidirectional-totp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/bidirectional-totp/</guid>
      <description>Image sourced from Wikimedia, attributed according to the Creative Commons Attribution 2.0 Generic license.
Motivation Time-Based One Time Password (TOTP) authentication is extremely beneficial. It lets you quickly add two‑factor authentication (2FA) to online accounts according to a simple and open standard. Simply scan a QR code into a TOTP app like Aegis. As long as you have access to your phone, you can then use the TOTP app to generate 2FA codes whenever need be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locked out of Keybase</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/locked-out-of-keybase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/locked-out-of-keybase/</guid>
      <description>Keybase I locked myself out of Keybase 🦝 If you get a message from juniperspring on Keybase, don&amp;rsquo;t trust it. See my GitHub gist for more info: https://gist.github.com/librick/8070876676dc02c83fea756fb78dd768.
I lost access to my Keybase account. I was playing around with the CLI and ran the following commands:
keybase account lockdown keybase logout Apparently those are bad commands to run when you&amp;rsquo;ve revoked all other devices and forgot your Keybase password. I still have keys for one of my devices, but AFAIK they&amp;rsquo;re encrypted with some secret derived from my Keybase password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Comment Injection in OpenWRT</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/ssh-comment-injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/ssh-comment-injection/</guid>
      <description>OpenWRT is open source router and Wi-Fi access point software. LuCI is the web-based configuration interface for OpenWRT; one of its features is the ability to import SSH keys. Instead of OpenSSH, OpenWRT uses Dropbear, an SSH server implementation optimized for embedded systems1.
OpenSSH 8.2, released Feb. 14th, 2020, added support for new FIDO public key types, such as &amp;ldquo;ecdsa-sk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ed25519-sk&amp;rdquo;2. I wanted to see if Dropbear supported these new key types.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
