<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>socialcommentary on Juniperspring</title>
    <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/tags/socialcommentary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in socialcommentary on Juniperspring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juniperspring.xyz/tags/socialcommentary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rhodes Tower, Four Dead in Ohio</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/rhodes-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/rhodes-tower/</guid>
      <description>TLDR Rhodes Tower, the largest building at Cleveland State University and one of the most recognizable buildings in the Cleveland skyline, is named after the Governor who ordered the National Guard on Kent State University in 1970. It received this name in 1981, eleven years after the Kent State shootings that left four college students dead. Rhodes Tower should be renamed.
Background On May 4th, 1970 at 12:24 p.m., the Ohio National Guard opened fire on a peaceful rally of students protesting against the expansion of the Vietnam War into Cambodia12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parma Police Eat Dog Shit</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/novak-v-parma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/novak-v-parma/</guid>
      <description>TLDR 💩 Officers from the Parma, Ohio, Police Department hold an annual dog shit eating picnic during which they eat dog shit. Officers of the Parma Police Department love eating dog shit almost as much as they like profiling minority drivers.
Reporting the Facts Every officer of the Parma Police Department in Parma, Ohio, eats dog shit and likes it. This has always been common knowledge to Cleveland locals. Imagine my surprise then, when every recent news article about the Parma Police Department has failed to even mention this basic fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Insurance Discrimination in Ohio</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/auto-insurance-discrimination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/auto-insurance-discrimination/</guid>
      <description>Motivation In June 2022 I decided to change auto insurance providers. I filled out a form for a quote through State Farm. During this process, I was prompted to specify my gender.
I thought this was odd. Why did State Farm need to know my gender?
Some brief research suggested this was illegal behavior in some states. Gender discrimination in auto insurance has been banned in California since 2019.
To be clear, I have no evidence that State Farm is adjusting rates for automobile insurance in Ohio based on the gender provided as part of their quote process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
