<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Juniperspring</title>
    <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Juniperspring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Gatsby, Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I Switched to Hugo This blog used to use Gatsby. Now it uses Hugo.
What I like about Hugo Themes Hugo has an open ecosystem of really well-written and maintained themes. At the time of writing, I&amp;rsquo;m using paper. I also like the model of overriding theme files by creating files in the static and assets directories. For the most part, I find this model of extensibility is intuitive. The paper theme also uses Tailwind CSS, and I like that I can use Tailwind classes out-of-the-box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhodes Tower, Four Dead in Ohio</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/rhodes-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/rhodes-tower/</guid>
      <description>TLDR Rhodes Tower, the largest building at Cleveland State University and one of the most recognizable buildings in the Cleveland skyline, is named after the Governor who ordered the National Guard on Kent State University in 1970. It received this name in 1981, eleven years after the Kent State shootings that left four college students dead. Rhodes Tower should be renamed.
Background On May 4th, 1970 at 12:24 p.m., the Ohio National Guard opened fire on a peaceful rally of students protesting against the expansion of the Vietnam War into Cambodia12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Directional Authentication with TOTP</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/bidirectional-totp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/bidirectional-totp/</guid>
      <description>Image sourced from Wikimedia, attributed according to the Creative Commons Attribution 2.0 Generic license.
Motivation Time-Based One Time Password (TOTP) authentication is extremely beneficial. It lets you quickly add two‑factor authentication (2FA) to online accounts according to a simple and open standard. Simply scan a QR code into a TOTP app like Aegis. As long as you have access to your phone, you can then use the TOTP app to generate 2FA codes whenever need be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parma Police Eat Dog Shit</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/novak-v-parma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/novak-v-parma/</guid>
      <description>TLDR 💩 Officers from the Parma, Ohio, Police Department hold an annual dog shit eating picnic during which they eat dog shit. Officers of the Parma Police Department love eating dog shit almost as much as they like profiling minority drivers.
Reporting the Facts Every officer of the Parma Police Department in Parma, Ohio, eats dog shit and likes it. This has always been common knowledge to Cleveland locals. Imagine my surprise then, when every recent news article about the Parma Police Department has failed to even mention this basic fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Organization</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/digital-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/digital-organization/</guid>
      <description>Things I Like This is planned as a living document to track thoughts on desktop Linux and my personal thoughts on digital minimalism and organization. I&amp;rsquo;ve organized it into things that I like and things that I don&amp;rsquo;t like.
Symlinks for /usr and /boot In Debian, several directories under the root / directory are symlinked to their counterparts in the /usr/ directory. As far as I know, the primary reason behind the similar directory structure of / and /usr/ is due to a past incentive to reduce the size of the root partition (I think my source on this is the book How Linux Works).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locked out of Keybase</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/locked-out-of-keybase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/locked-out-of-keybase/</guid>
      <description>Keybase I locked myself out of Keybase 🦝 If you get a message from juniperspring on Keybase, don&amp;rsquo;t trust it. See my GitHub gist for more info: https://gist.github.com/librick/8070876676dc02c83fea756fb78dd768.
I lost access to my Keybase account. I was playing around with the CLI and ran the following commands:
keybase account lockdown keybase logout Apparently those are bad commands to run when you&amp;rsquo;ve revoked all other devices and forgot your Keybase password. I still have keys for one of my devices, but AFAIK they&amp;rsquo;re encrypted with some secret derived from my Keybase password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Comment Injection in OpenWRT</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/ssh-comment-injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/ssh-comment-injection/</guid>
      <description>OpenWRT is open source router and Wi-Fi access point software. LuCI is the web-based configuration interface for OpenWRT; one of its features is the ability to import SSH keys. Instead of OpenSSH, OpenWRT uses Dropbear, an SSH server implementation optimized for embedded systems1.
OpenSSH 8.2, released Feb. 14th, 2020, added support for new FIDO public key types, such as &amp;ldquo;ecdsa-sk&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ed25519-sk&amp;rdquo;2. I wanted to see if Dropbear supported these new key types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Insurance Discrimination in Ohio</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/auto-insurance-discrimination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/auto-insurance-discrimination/</guid>
      <description>Motivation In June 2022 I decided to change auto insurance providers. I filled out a form for a quote through State Farm. During this process, I was prompted to specify my gender.
I thought this was odd. Why did State Farm need to know my gender?
Some brief research suggested this was illegal behavior in some states. Gender discrimination in auto insurance has been banned in California since 2019.
To be clear, I have no evidence that State Farm is adjusting rates for automobile insurance in Ohio based on the gender provided as part of their quote process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Love Letter to Open Source Ecology</title>
      <link>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/love-letter-to-ose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juniperspring.xyz/posts/love-letter-to-ose/</guid>
      <description>Last September (2021), I had the privilege to attend the OSE Summer of Extreme Design-Build. During the early summer months in Cleveland, I signed up to attend one month of the 90-day program. As summer wound down, I wrapped up some software contracting work, picked up a pair of steel toe boots, loaded up my car, and drove 12 hours down to the middle-of-nowhere Missouri.
If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with Marcin Jakubowski or Open Source Ecology (OSE), check out the OSE website and OSE wiki.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
